http://spivalaw.com/privacy-policy/

Skip Navigation
HomeAbout Us Firm OverviewHoward SpivaCecil Clay DavisClay PorterMary HashemiGene SpivaJennifer McKibbanSee All Team MembersJoin Our Team!Legal Services Personal Injury LawyerCar Accident LawyerTruck Accident LawyerBrain Injury LawyerChild Injury LawyerIndustrial Site Injury LawyerSpinal Injury LawyerWorkers’ Compensation LawyerSee All Cases We TakeCommunityBlogContact UsCall UsDirectionsLogin
MENU
CALL FOR A FREE CONSULTATION
912-920-2000
Live Chat Client Portal
Charity Store
About Us Firm OverviewHoward SpivaCecil Clay DavisClay PorterMary HashemiGene SpivaSee All Team MembersJoin Our Team!Legal Services Personal Injury LawyerCar Accident LawyerTruck Accident LawyerBrain Injury LawyerChild Injury AttorneyIndustrial Site Injury LawyerSpinal Injury LawyerWorkers’ Compensation LawyerSee All Cases We TakeCommunity NewslettersBlogContact UsHome Privacy Privacy PolicyThe Spiva Law Group PC thanks you for visiting this web site. The Spiva Law Group PC is committed to protecting your privacy while providing you with a positive on-line experience. The Spiva Law Group PC respects your privacy, and we believe you have the right to know what information we collect, how we use it and what security measures we have taken to protect your information.Collection and Use of InformationWhen you visit www.spivalaw.com and use our Contact Form, certain information may be collected. Among the types of information that may be collected are:Domain names of visitors to our site;Your name, address, e-mail address and additional information you provide in the form;“Navigational information” regarding the traffic patterns of our site, including the number of visits to a particular page and user-specific information on which pages a guest visits, average length of time spent on the site and similar site usage data; andAny information that you may choose to submit in connection with any e-mail messages, on-site surveys, registry programs, contests and the like.The Spiva Law Group PC uses this information to help us develop and improve our site to better meet your needs. We may use your name or e-mail address to contact you or respond to your inquiries. We also use this information to help us diagnose technical issues relating to the performance of our website.Providing Information to Outside PartiesThe Spiva Law Group PC does not sell, trade, rent or otherwise provide your personal information to any outside parties.SecurityThe Spiva Law Group PC makes every effort to protect the security of your personal information. Any personal information you provide will not be stored on our server. Any information collected by us is stored in private files behind a firewall designed to protect your information by denying unauthorized access by outside users.Updates and Removing Your NameIf you do not wish to receive e-mails from the Spiva Law Group PC in the future please let us know by contacting us.Get Help TodayName*
First Email* Phone*How Can We Help You?
Meet Our Attorneys
Howard Spiva
Cecil Clay Davis
Clay Porter
Mary Hashemi
MEET YOUR SUPPORT TEAMOur Cause: Justice For Children FoundationLearn how Howard Spiva's "Heads In Helmets" Charity Program keeps kids safe and prevents children's brain injuries. Learn More about Our Cause
Associations & Awards
Free Consultation placeholderConnect With UsCall TodayGet DirectionsOffice Hours
sm-facebook
sm-twitter
sm-youtube
sm-linkedin
Free Consultation© 2020 Spiva Law Group PC – All Rights Reserved. placeholderVisit Our Savannah Office
Spiva Law Group PC 1137 Mohawk Street Savannah, GA 31419 912-920-2000©2017 Spiva Law Group PC – All Rights Reserved.TV & Radio InterviewsFAQsWatch Our VideosVerdicts & ResultsClient TestimonialsJoin Our Team!Site MapDisclaimerPrivacy Policy
Site by Consultwebs.com: Law Firm Website Designers / Personal Injury
Lawyer Marketing. × × ×Office Hours Monday8:30 AM - 5:30 PMTuesday8:30 AM - 5:30 PMWednesday8:30 AM - 5:30 PMThursday8:30 AM - 5:30 PMFriday8:30 AM - 5:30 PMSaturdayClosedSundayClosed
